To answer this question let's look closely at the data.
为了解答这个问题 我们来仔细查看数据
It seems that the red and green dots are nicely separated by a line.
红色的点和绿色的点似乎可以被一条线很好地分开
Here is the line and we can see that most points over it are green,
我们可以看出在这条线上方的大部分点是绿色的
whereas most points under it are red, with some exceptions.
而下方的大部分点是红色的 但有些数据点例外
So that line is going to be our model and from now on, every time we get
我们以条线为模型 每当接到新的学生申请
a new student, we check their scores and plot them in this graph.
我们把他们的成绩画在坐标图上
If they end up over the line, we predict that they'll get accepted.
如果数据点是在这条线的上方 那么预测他们会被录取
And if they end up below the line, we predict that they'll get rejected.
如果数据点是在下方 则预测他们会被拒绝
So, since student three ends up here and the point with coordinate seven and
学生 3 的数据坐标为 (7, 6)
six which is over the line, we conclude that the string gets accepted.
位于直线上方 因此我们判断这个学生会被录取
So, if you said yes, that is the correct answer.
如果你的回答是肯定的 那么它是正确答案
This method is known as, Logistic Regression.
这种方法叫做逻辑回归 (Logistic Regression)
And now the question is, how do we find this line that best cuts the data?
现在的问题是 我们如何找到这条能最好地分割数据点的线？
So let's look at a simple example, how do we draw the line that
来看一个简单的例子
best separates the green points from the red points?
如何画出一条线以最好地区分绿色数据点和红色数据点？
Well again the computer can't really eyeball the line.
计算机无法依靠视觉来画出这条线
And so, we can start by drawing a random line like this one.
所以我们从画一条像这样的随机的线开始
And now given this line, let's randomly say that we label the region
有了这条线 我们再随机地规定
over the line as green and the region under the line as red.
位于线的上方的点为绿色 下方的点为红色
So just with linear regression,
然后就像线性回归那样
we'll first try to see how bad this first line is.
我们先计算这条线的效果
A simple measure of how bad the line is, is just the number of errors.
一个简单的测量误差的标准是出错的数目
That is, the number of misclassified points.
即被错误归类的数据点的数量
This line misclassified two points, one red and one green.
这条线错判了两个点 一个红色的点和一个绿色的点
So we'll say, it has two errors.
因此我们说它有两个错误
And again with linear regression.
仍然与线性回归类似
What we'll do is, move the line around trying to minimize the number of errors,
我们移动这条线 通过梯度下降算法
using gradient descent.
最小化错误数量
So if we move the line a bit in this direction,
如果沿着这个方向稍微移动这条线
we can see that we start correctly classifying one of the points,
我们可以看到它开始能正确地归类其中一个数据点
bringing down the number of errors to one.
把错误数目降低到了一个
And if we move it even more, we correctly classify the other one
如果继续移动这条线 它正确归类了另一个点
of the points, bringing down the number of errors to zero.
错误数目被降低到了零
In reality, in order to properly use the gradient descent method,
实际使用中 为了正确地使用梯度下降算法
it turns out the number of errors is not what we need to minimize.
我们需要最小化的并不是错误数目
But instead,
取而代之的是
something that captures the number of errors called log loss function.
能代表错误数目的对数损失函数 (log loss function)
Let's actually study that in more detail.
我们进行更仔细的学习
So here are our six points again with four of them correctly classified,
这里有六个数据点 其中四个被正确归类
two red and two green and
它们是两个红色和两个绿色
two of them incorrectly classified, one red and one green.
两个被错误归类 它们是一个红色和一个绿色
The error function will assign a large penalty to the two incorrectly
误差函数会对这两个被错误归类的数据点施加很大的惩罚
classified points and small penalty to the four correctly classified points.
而对四个被正确归类的点施加很小的惩罚
We'll actually learn the formula for the error function in the class.
在这门课程中我们将会正式地学习误差函数公式
Now we obtain the error function by adding all the errors
我们现在使用所有数据点的错误之和作为误差函数
from the corresponding points, here we obtain a large
我们得到一个很大的误差值
number since the two misclassified points add a lot to the error function.
因为两个被错判的点带来很大的误差
Now the idea is to, jiggle the line around to minimize this error.
现在四处移动这条线以将误差降到最小
So if we move the line in this direction,
如果我们沿着这个方向移动这条线
we can see that some errors decrease and some slightly increase.
可以看到误差有些误差减小了 有些则微微增加了
But in general, when we consider the sum, the sum gets smaller since we've
但总体上 误差之和变小了
correctly classified the two points that were misclassified before.
因为我们正确地归类了之前被错判的两个点
So the point of this process is,
这个过程的意图是
to find the best line fit by minimizing the error function.
找出能最小化误差函数的最佳拟合线
And how do we minimize the error function?
我们如何最小化误差函数？
Again, with gradient descent.
依旧是使用梯度下降算法
So once more, here we are at the summit of Mount Errorest,
我们再次回到珠穆朗玛峰顶
we're quite high up, because our error is large, we're you can see,
我们所在的位置很高 因为此时有很大的误差
how the height is the sum of the green and red areas.
这可以从绿色和红色区域之和的大小中看出
So, we explore around to see what direction brings us down the most or
我们探索四周寻找下降最大的方向
equivalently.
或者等价地
What direction can we move the line in order to reduce the error the most?
寻找能通过移动直线最大程度减小误差的方向
And we decide to take a step in that direction.
我们决定沿着这个方向前进一步
So now, we're misclassifying only one of the points.
现在只有一个点被错误地归类
We can see how that decreases our function, bringing us down the mountain.
我们可以看到这种方法如何减小误差函数 把我们从山顶上带下来
And we do it again,
我们继续这样做
we take a step in the direction that reduces the arrow the most.
沿着最大程度减小误差的方向前进一步
Now, we're at the bottom of the mountains,
就到达了山底
since we were reduced the error twist minimum, possible value.
因为我们已经将误差减少到了最小值